## Varun Kumar

+91 8126178902 | MauryaTech1710@Gmail.com | Dehradun, Dehradun, Uttarakhand

## Summary

Experienced Computer Engineer and a good Developer. Always focused on improving myself and my skills. Dedicated Computer Engineer with more than 2 years of experience in self business.

Having good knowledge of Computer Hardware and Web Designing. I developed many project on college level including Group Projects, like College Website, e-learning platform, Random Password Generator, etc.

## **Experience**

## MauryaTech | Dehradun, Uttarakhand

## Computer Hardware Engineer | 08/2017 - 03/2022

This was a business where i design new Computer Systems and repair the problems in computer hardware. Here i build design new Computer Systems and repair the problems in computer hardware. Here i build many new Computer Systems and repair the problems in computer hardware. Here i build many system for particular works like gaming and office works.

## NSS | Dehradun, Uttarakhand

#### Camera Operator and Editor | 03/2022 - 03/2022

NSS, National Service Scheme. Here in a camp of NSS i selected as Camera operator and editor. In this camp journey i click the picture and videos i click the picture and videos and edit them according to requirement.

## SGRR Public School | Dehradun, Uttarakhand

## Volunteer | 02/2019 - 04/2019

Performed wide range of administrative, analytical and support duties and function relating to various aspects of organization.

Encourage people to be active in community through organizational events and projects.

## Skills

Microsoft excel, Microsoft word, Leadership, Programming language C, PHP Programming Language, C++ Programming Language, Java Programming Language, Photoshop\, Photography

#### Education

# Government Polytechnic Dehradun | Dehradun, Uttarakhand Information Technology | 07/2022

In Government Polytechnic Dehradun, i pursued Diploma in Information Technology pursued Diploma in Information Technology. Technology pursued Diploma in Information Technology. In this field i learned many things and skills like how to secure computer system and our data programming languages, etc.

### Languages

English, Hindi

## Certificates

JAVA Programming Language, LetsUpgrade 3 days Program on Responsive Website, CyberSecurity Program, Full Stack Webdevelopment Internship Training, Python Vocational Training